// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
      question: "If i had study hard , i might perfect the exam",
      answer: "Type C",
      options: [
        "Type O",
        "Type A",
        "Type B",
        "Type C",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
      question: "If she aced the test, she should have been studied hard",
      answer: "Type A",
      options: [
        "Type O",
        "Type A",
        "Type B",
        "Type C",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
      question: "I may have aced the test and may have ranked 1 if i just had diligently studied",
      answer: "Type C",
      options: [
        "Type O",
        "Type A",
        "Type B",
        "Type C",
      ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
      question: "If shan have money, he might buy a shoes",
      answer: "Type A",
      options: [
        "Type O",
        "Type A",
        "Type B",
        "Type C",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
      question: "If you work too much, you'll exhaust",
      answer: "Type O",
      options: [
        "Type O",
        "Type A",
        "Type B",
        "Type C",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
      question: " If Tom passed the board exam, he should have a lisence now",
      answer: "Type A",
      options: [
        "Type O",
        "Type A",
        "Type B",
        "Type C",
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 7,
      question: " Use general truth",
      answer: "Type O",
      options: [
        "Type O",
        "Type A",
        "Type B",
        "Type C",
      ]
  },
{
    numb: 8,
      question: " Use imaginary situation",
      answer: "Type B",
      options: [
        "Type O",
        "Type A",
        "Type B",
        "Type C",
      ]
  },
{
      numb: 9,
      question: "Use regret in the past",
      answer: "Type C",
      options: [
      "Type O",
        "Type A",
        "Type B",
        "Type C",
      ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
      question: "Use future event",
      answer: "Type A",
      options: [
      "Type O",
        "Type A",
        "Type B",
        "Type C",
    ]
  },

  // you can make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];